intego.com 2018-10-04

# Intego Privacy Policy

Intego is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the data of its clients, associates, suppliers, and website visitors. We want you to understand how we collect and use information from our website so you can interact with Intego with confidence. By using Intego’s website (“Site”) you accept and agree to the practices this Privacy Policy describes.

## Information We Collect

When you use our Site, we may collect and use personally identifiable information about you, as well as other information. “Personally identifiable information” includes your name, email address, telephone number, mailing address, and other similar information that can be used to identify you. More specifically, when you use our Site, we may collect and store the following information:

  * Transactional information based on your activities on the Site (including but not limited to purchases you make, purchase content, and searches conducted, as related to your account activity)
  * Correspondence sent to us through the Site
  * IP addresses
  * Browser type
  * Computer operating system
  * Web log information
  * Date and time you visit the website
  * Other click-stream data

## Consent and Use of Your Information

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

When you provide us with personal information to become a partner or an affiliate, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will ask you directly for your expressed consent.

You may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [support@intego.com](mailto:support@intego.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy:%20Request%20to%20Withdraw%20From%20the%20Marketing%20Newsletter).

## FastSpring

Our e-store is hosted on FastSpring. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

The following information is stored with FastSpring:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Mailing Address
  * Physical Location
  * Company name
  * Job Title
  * Phone Number
  * Financial information, such as credit card or payment methods, depending on the requirements of the service used

Your data is stored through FastSpring’s data storage, databases and the general FastSpring application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then FastSpring stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS).

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read FastSpring’s Terms of Service [here](https://fastspring.com/terms-use/) or Privacy Statement [here](https://fastspring.com/privacy/).

## How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it.

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to sites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit [allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

When you are on one of the Intego partner websites, we do not collect cookies nor use them for ad serving.

## Security

We use commercially suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on our Site. These procedures include, but are not limited to, encryption, SSL (secure socket layer), passwords, and physical security. We also limit access to any personally identifiable information we receive to employees who need access to that information in order to do their jobs. However, no data protection procedures are entirely infallible. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee that it will be 100% secure.

## Sharing Your Information

With the exception of data noted above under the “FastSpring” section used to facilitate subscriptions of paid customers, we do not share any personally identifiable information with any third parties.

We may share aggregated non-identifiable information about our general readership with third parties in order to help market our products and develop new vendor and customer relationships.

We do not sell or rent personal information collected through Intego’s Site to anyone.

Other Circumstances: We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party, or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to:

  * Comply with applicable laws, regulations, legal process (such as a subpoena), or enforceable government request;
  * Enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations of such Terms, or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; and
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of Intego, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

## Third-Party Websites and Social Media Features

Intego’s Site may contain links to other sites, including those of third parties or business partners such as Facebook, Twitter, etc. While we seek to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices other websites use. By accessing other third party websites or applications through our Site, you are consenting to the terms and privacy policies of those websites. It is possible that other parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use Intego’s Site.

## Review and Correction of Your Information

You may review and edit the information Intego collected about you at any time. If your information has been shared with a third party, as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, then that third party has received its own copy of your data. If you have been contacted by one of these third parties and wish to correct or delete your information, please contact them directly. To receive a summary of the information you've provided to Intego, click here. To submit a request to erase your information, click here. To receive a summary of your payment information stored with FastSpring, contact [privacy@fastspring.com](mailto:privacy@fastspring.com) or see [FastSpring Privacy Policy](https://fastspring.com/privacy/) for more details. To submit a request to erase the payment information you have stored with FastSpring, contact [privacy@fastspring.com](mailto:privacy@fastspring.com)  
or see [FastSpring Privacy Policy](https://fastspring.com/privacy/) for more details. Please note that erasing your payment information with FastSpring will result in the termination of your subscription.

## California Privacy Rights

California law allows California residents to ask companies with whom they have an established business relationship to provide certain information about the companies’ sharing of personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. Intego does not share any California consumer personal information with third parties for marketing purposes without consent.

California customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about our privacy practices may contact us using the contact information set forth below.

## Users Only of Legal Age of Majority

Our Site is intended for a general audience over 18 years of age and is not directed to children under 13 years of age.  We do not intend to collect personal information as defined by the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) (“Children’s Personal Information”) in a manner that is not permitted by COPPA, and for any children’s or mixed-use portions of our Site (if any) we will comply with COPPA.  If you are a parent or guardian and believe we have collected Children’s Personal Information in a manner not permitted by COPPA, please contact us at the address listed below (Attention: Legal) and we will remove such data to the extent required by COPPA.

Parents may want to consider commercially available parental control protections to limit what minors can access online and/or monitor their minor children’s online activities. We recommend Intego ContentBarrier.

## Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 10, 2018.

We update the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. If we materially change our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by contacting you through your user account e-mail address or by posting a notice on our Site. Your continued use of the Site will be deemed your agreement that your information may be used in accordance with the new policy. If you do not agree with the changes, then you should stop using the Site and notify us that you do not want your information used in accordance with the changes.

## Contacting Us

Please contact us at [support@intego.com](mailto:support@intego.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy:%20Questions%20/%20Comments) to submit any questions, comments, or complaints you may have regarding this Privacy Policy.

Additional contacts, including the mailing address and contact number, may be found by visiting our Contact Page.
